{
    "Rounds":[
        {"RoundNumber": 1,
        "RoundName":"Topical",
        "Questions":[
            {
                "QuestionNumber": 1,
                "Question":"This year sees the 50th anniversary of the Apollo 11 moon landing. How many days did it take Neil Armstrong and his crew to get to the moon?",
                "AnswerOptions": {
                    "A": "4",
                    "B": "5",
                    "C": "7",
                    "D": "8"
                },
                "Answer":"A"},
            {
                "QuestionNumber": 2,
                "Question":"New York City suffered a black out at the weekend, just like on the same day 42 years earlier. But what was one of the causes of this one?",
                "AnswerOptions": {
                    "A": "Some sort of fire",
                    "B": "Donald Trump, great guy",
                    "C": "Subway derailment",
                    "D": "Someone plugging in their phone charger"
                },
                "Answer":"A"},
            {
                "QuestionNumber": 3,
                "Question":"The re-make of The Lion King is released on Friday. Donald Glover is the voice of Simba, but how is he related to Danny Glover?",
                "AnswerOptions": {
                    "A": "Son",
                    "B": "Nephew",
                    "C": "Grandson",
                    "D": "Heâ€™s not"
                },
                "Answer":"D"},
            {
                "QuestionNumber": 4,
                "Question":"On Friday it was announced that Facebook is to be fined for its Cambridge Analytica privacy violations. How much is the fine? ðŸ‘Ž",
                "AnswerOptions": {
                    "A": "$3 billion",
                    "B": "$4 billion",
                    "C": "$5 billion",
                    "D": "$100 billion"
                },
                "Answer":"C"}
        ]},
        {"RoundNumber": 2,
            "RoundName":"Sport",
            "Questions":[
                {
                    "QuestionNumber": 1,
                    "Question":"Serena Williams and Andy Murray teamed up in the mixed doubles this year at Wimbledon. But which round did they make it to?",
                    "AnswerOptions": {
                        "A": "2nd",
                        "B": "3rd",
                        "C": "Quarterfinals",
                        "D": "Semifinals"
                    },
                    "Answer":"B"},
                {
                    "QuestionNumber": 2,
                    "Question":"How many runs did England win by to beat New Zealand in the Cricket World Cup?",
                    "AnswerOptions": {
                        "A": "0",
                        "B": "1",
                        "C": "2",
                        "D": "3"
                    },
                    "Answer":"A"},
                {
                    "QuestionNumber": 3,
                    "Question":"St.Helens Rugby League team beat Wigan for the third time this season so far.  But how many points are they currently clear at the top of the table",
                    "AnswerOptions": {
                        "A": "4",
                        "B": "6",
                        "C": "8",
                        "D": "10"
                    },
                    "Answer":"D"},
                {
                    "QuestionNumber": 4,
                    "Question":"Lewis Hamilton has just broken the record for the most Formula 1 wins at Silverstone, but how times has he now won there?",
                    "AnswerOptions": {
                        "A": "4",
                        "B": "5",
                        "C": "6",
                        "D": "7"
                    },
                    "Answer":"C"}
        ]},
        {"RoundNumber": 3,
            "RoundName":"Music",
            "Questions":[
                {
                    "QuestionNumber": 1,
                    "Question":"In which film does this song appear?",
                    "AnswerOptions": {
                        "A": "Despicable Me 1",
                        "B": "Despicable Me 2",
                        "C": "Despicable Me 3",
                        "D": "Toy Story"
                    },
                    "Answer":"B"},
                {
                    "QuestionNumber": 2,
                    "Question":"Which of these 80s anthems had the highest UK chart position on itâ€™s original release?",
                    "AnswerOptions": {
                        "A": "Kids in America, Kim wilde (2)",
                        "B": "Eye of the Tiger, Survivor",
                        "C": "Donâ€™t Stop Believing, journey",
                        "D": "Vienna, Ultravox "
                    },
                    "Answer":"B"},
                {
                    "QuestionNumber": 3,
                    "Question":"Which Amy Winehouse song did Miley Cyrus cover at Glastonbury this year?",
                    "AnswerOptions": {
                        "A": "Rehab",
                        "B": "Back to Black",
                        "C": "You Know I'm No Good",
                        "D": "Valerie"
                    },
                    "Answer":"B"},
                {
                    "QuestionNumber": 4,
                    "Question":"Which year did this song first get to number one?",
                    "AnswerOptions": {
                        "A": "1988",
                        "B": "1989",
                        "C": "1990",
                        "D": "1991"
                    },
                    "Answer":"B"}
        ]}
    ]
}
    